In this exercise, you'll be asked to create an S3 bucket and then apply
在此练习中 将要求您创建 S3 存储区 然后应用
an S3 lifecycle policy to that bucket to delete items in it after a number of days.
对该存储区的 S3 生命周期策略 以在若干天后删除其中的项
Here we have an example S3 bucket.
这里有一个例子 S3 桶
If you'd look at the Management tab within the user interface,
如果您在用户界面中查看 " 管理 " 选项卡
we'll see that our first option is for Lifecycle.
我们会看到我们的第一个选择是生命周期
Underneath we have a Add lifecycle rule button.
下面是 " 添加生命周期规则 " 按钮
Clicking this button, brings us to this wizard for creating a lifecycle rule.
单击此按钮将使我们进入此向导以创建生命周期规则
First thing we do is we'll name our rule.
首先我们会把规则命名
Then we're asked if you want to limit the scope to
那我们就问你要把范围限制到
specific subsection of the bucket or just apply this to the entire bucket?
还是把这个给整个桶子
We're just going apply it to the entire bucket.
我们要把它应用到整个桶里
Next will go onto the second stage of the lifecycle rule wizard.
接下来 将进入生命周期规则向导的第二个阶段
The second stage, as we see on the top, is called transitions.
第二个阶段 正如我们在顶部看到的 称为转换
This stage is for transitioning objects from one storage class to another,
此阶段用于将对象从一个存储类转换为另一个存储类
is not about expiring or deleting objects.
不是关于到期或删除对象
So actually we're just going to skip through this step of the wizard.
实际上 我们将跳过向导的这个步骤
The third part of the wizard is for expiration.
向导的第三部分是到期的
So this is where we can expire or again,
这就是我们可以到期的地方
delete objects. One last note.
删除对象  最后一张
In this case, we are not talking about a versioned S3 bucket,
在这种情况下 我们不是在谈论一个版本化的 S3 桶
so we're only concerned with the current version for this exercise. Good luck.
所以我们只关心这次演习的最新版本 祝你好运